Carlos Borrega

JavaScript Web Developer

c.borrega@pm.me | 07599306711 | www.borrega.io | London N16

Summary	•

I am a self-taught, JavaScript Web Developer with 1 and a half years of coding experience. I have built several projects listed on my portfolio where I use a variety of coding languages to achieve different outcomes.

I have past work experience as a retail assistant manager and visual merchandiser for more than 9 years, where I had the chance of developing my communication skills and team building abilities. Having worked in high paced environments, I was able to demonstrate my creative problem-solving and adaptability to unexpected changes.

Programming Skills _____

- Languages: JavaScript, CSS, HTML
- Frameworks: Bootstrap, jQuery, Express
- Tools: VS Code, Hyper, NodeJS, MongoDB, Git, GitHub

Experience _____

Web Development Projects (available on www.borrega.io)

- 1. Infodex | www.borrega.io/infodex.html
 - NodeJS application with an open API to fetch Pokémon information.
- 2. Rock, Paper, Scissors | www.borrega.io/jsgame.html
 - JavaScript Game.
- 3. Portfolio | www.borrega.io/portfolio.html
 - Portfolio website for a textile designer.

Assistant Store Manager - Fred Perry | August 2019 - Present

 Responsible for employee hiring and training, schedules, banking duties and online customer service support.

Visual Merchandiser Manager - & Other Stories, Weekday, Club Monaco | June 2013 – August 2019

- Responsible for keeping the brands high standards and commerciality with weekly store flips, window dressing and mannequin styling.
- Planning and organising the visual merchandising team, training the store staff in maintenance routines and performing new store openings in the UK and Sweden.

Education _____

London App Brewery, London | December 2021 - October 2022

• Web Development Bootcamp

Escola Superior de Disseny ESDi, Barcelona | September 2008 – June 2011

- Bachelor's Degree in Personal and Corporate Image Consulting
- Master's degree in Styling, Image and Fashion Communication